# PERSONAL PROFILE

With my passion for creating exceptional user experiences and my proficiency in a wide range of frontend technologies, I believe I would be a valuable addition to your team. My professional experience as a frontend developer, combined with my educational background in CS, has equipped me with the skills and knowledge necessary to excel in this role. Over the past 2 years, I have been responsible for designing, developing and maintaining user-friendly, responsive, and visually appealing websites and web application for a variety of clients.



### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### CONSULTANT, IOS DEVELOPER - MARCH 2019- AUG 2019

As a junior developer, I worked on a flexible Electronic Flight Bag system. I worked on different customization and adjustments for our customers. App maintenance was done using git.

### Responsibility areas:

- Customization of the EFB for our customers
- Time-estimation of tasks
- Maintenance of the system

#### JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER, ELEMENT - MARCH 2019- AUG 2019

I worked as a javascript front-end developer. I worked in A agile and energetic environment. My stack was HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript.

### Responsibility areas:

- Used html, css, js to add new features like anchor navigations, live chats. I created SPA using reactJS by converting Figma designs to web apps.
- Constantly improving codebase to ensure high maintainability and extensibility, optimizing of existing functions the frontend.
- Time-estimation of tasks
- Maintenance of sites

#### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER: BOOKANYBOAT.COM - JUL 2023 - NOW

Bookanyboat is a B2B booking system to seamlessly manage bookings for stakeholders. Tjenestenen sparret dem tid og penge. Udover det kunne mine kompetencer også bruges på flere områder i deres it-landskab.

#### Mine ansvarsområder:

- Worked the MVC data-structure and integrated the Mysql DB.
- I implemented other services such authentication using ruby on rails.
- Time-estimation of tasks
- Code maintenance
- Deployment of the application to heroku

### **EDUCATION**

H.C ØRESTAD TECHNICAL GYMNASIUM - 2013-2016 ROSKILDE UNIVERSITY - 2018- 2021 LE WAGON SOFTWARE BOOTCAMP - JUL - SEPT 2023

## **KOMPETENCER**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, React, NextJS, NodeJS, Git, Tailwind, Prisma, MongoDB, Redux, GraphQL, Apollo, Express, PostgreSQL, Python, Django, Framer Motion, Agile, Ancible, Puppet, PHP, Nginx, Chef, CI/CD pipelines, C++, Kubernetes

# **LANGUAGES**

Dansk: Modersmål

Kirundi: Modersmål

Fransk: Modersmål

Engelsk: Flydende i skrift og tale

# PRIVATE & SPARETIME

I'm a 27 year old bachelor. I live in Copenhagen, Denmark. In my sparetime I like to workout, do some readings, spend time with my family and friends. I enjoy watching and playing basketball and football. On Sundays I'm mostly in my local church, where I sing and play keyboard in a gospel band.

## **CONTACT**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jordy-sabimana-5b5500136/

https://github.com/jordysabimana